Hindsight is 2020.
Eddington is a western, comedy, crime film directed by Ari Aster.
In May of 2020, a standoff between a small-town sheriff and mayor sparks a powder
keg as neighbor is pitted against neighbor in Eddington, New Mexico.
Joe Cross, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Dawn Bodkin, played by Deirdre O'Connell.
Louise Cross, played by Emma Stone.
Michael Cooke, played by Micheal Ward.
Ted Garcia, played by Pedro Pascal.
Brian Frazee, played by Cameron Mann.
Eddington is a 2025 American satirical neo-Western thriller film written and directed by Ari Aster, and starring
Joaquin Phoenix, Pedro Pascal, Luke Grimes, Deirdre O'Connell, Micheal Ward, Austin Butler, and Emma Stone.
Set in 2020 during the COVID-19 pandemic in New Mexico, the film examines the political and social turmoil
caused by the contested mayoral election fought between Sheriff Joe Cross and Mayor Ted Garcia.
The film had its world premiere at the main competition of the 2025 Cannes Film Festival
on May 16, 2025, and was released in theaters by A24 on July 18, 2025.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics
and has grossed $13.7 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of small town, sheriff, husband
wife relationship, new mexico, mayor.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.